<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Qibo, tell me why: the app that answers all your child &#34;why?&#34; questions</title>
    <link>https://askqibo.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Qibo, tell me why: the app that answers all your child &#34;why?&#34; questions</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>The Qibo app and brand is the intellectual property of Unstatic Labs and its creators © 2022-2023</copyright><atom:link href="https://askqibo.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Service and Use for the Super Tester Program</title>
      <link>https://askqibo.com/super-tester/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askqibo.com/super-tester/</guid>
      <description>By participating in the Super Tester program for the Qibo app (&amp;ldquo;the Program&amp;rdquo;), you acknowledge and agree to be bound by these terms of service and use (&amp;ldquo;Terms&amp;rdquo;) as well as our usual Terms of Use. If you do not agree to these Terms, you may not participate in the Program.
Purpose of the Program The Program is a paid subscription service provided by Unstatic Labs and its creators with no warranty of service (including availability, accuracy, or responsiveness).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Privacy Policy</title>
      <link>https://askqibo.com/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askqibo.com/privacy/</guid>
      <description>By accessing or using the &amp;ldquo;Qibo&amp;rdquo; (&amp;ldquo;Tell me why&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Dis pourquoi&amp;rdquo;) application (&amp;ldquo;the App&amp;rdquo;), you agree to this Privacy Policy (&amp;ldquo;Policy&amp;rdquo;). If you do not agree to this Policy, you may not use the App.
The App is distributed by Unstatic Labs and its creators (&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rdquo;) without warranties of any kind.
Information We Collect We do not collect any personal information from users of the App, including voice recordings or any personal information provided through the use of the speech-to-text technology.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Credits: Copyright and Licenses</title>
      <link>https://askqibo.com/credits/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askqibo.com/credits/</guid>
      <description>The Qibo brand and logo are the intellectual property of Unstatic Labs, created by Valentin Viennot and Roget Miret Giné ((c) 2022-2023).
Illustrations All original illustrations featured in the Qibo app and websites are the intellectual property of Unstatic Labs and its creators.
All non-original illustrations are licensed under CC BY terms:
The Qibo character and animation is the creation of Kirill Meshkov (rockingelevator), named &amp;ldquo;Quiz Time&amp;rdquo; and licensed under CC-BY 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mandatory information</title>
      <link>https://askqibo.com/mentions/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askqibo.com/mentions/</guid>
      <description>The Qibo app and website are published by Unstatic Labs and its creators Roger Miret Giné and Valentin Viennot.
This website is hosted on GitHub Pages and governed by french law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terms of Use</title>
      <link>https://askqibo.com/tou/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askqibo.com/tou/</guid>
      <description>By accessing or using the &amp;ldquo;Qibo&amp;rdquo; (&amp;ldquo;Tell me why&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Dis pourquoi&amp;rdquo;) application (&amp;ldquo;the App&amp;rdquo;), you agree to be bound by these terms of use (&amp;ldquo;Terms&amp;rdquo;). If you do not agree to these Terms, you may not use the App.
The App is distributed by Unstatic Labs and its creators, Roger Miret Giné and Valentin Viennot, (&amp;ldquo;We&amp;rdquo;) under private copyright.
DISCLAIMER THE APP AND THE CONTENT AND MATERIALS PROVIDED BY THE APP ARE PROVIDED &amp;ldquo;AS IS&amp;rdquo; AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Us</title>
      <link>https://askqibo.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://askqibo.com/contact/</guid>
      <description> Email: Message: Send </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
